Association of Liberated Librarians Records 157
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Association of Liberated Librarians Records
1953-1997
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Association of Liberated Librarians
157
0.75 Linear feet
3 Boxes
Biographical / Historical
The Association of Liberation Librarians (ALL) was a group of librarians "liberated" from the 9-to 5 routine - retired, self-employed, part-time employed, unemployed, an occasional student who met monthly and visited libraries, archives and galleries in the Washington, D.C. area. ALL began in 1981 as a subgroup of the Metropolitan Washington Council of Government's Metropolitan Library Council. The founding members were retirees, part-timers, contractors and freelance librarians, all of whom were acquainted with each other through membership in the District of Columbia Library Association (DCLA) and the Special Libraries Association (SLA) DC chapter. The original intent of ALL was not limited to fellowship and site visits - it also included service as a clearinghouse for volunteer and part-time work opportunities for its members and information of particular interest to retirees.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes organizational documents made and collected by the Association of Liberation Librarians (ALL). This includes bylaws, membership and job/volunteer announcements, meeting minutes and reports, newsletters, correspondence, and material relating to site visits. Since many of the organizers and later leaders of the Association of Liberated Librarians (ALL) also held leadership positions in both the District of Columbia Library Association (DCLA) and the DC Chapter of the Special Libraries Association (SLA), this collection also includes some organizational material from these organizations.
Custodial History
Provenance unknown.
Arrangement
Series 1: Bylaws and Organization Series 2: Correspondence Series 3: Ephemera Series 4: Meeting Minutes Series 5: Membership Series 6: Newsletters Series 7: Programs Series 8: Site Visits Series 9: Peripheral Organizations
Librarians; Libraries; Societies and clubs; Correspondence; Organizational Records; Ephemera; Minutes (Records)
- Series 1: Bylaws and Organization
  - Bylaws and Organization (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALL (The Association of Liberated Librarian) description/introduction, undated (Item 1)
- Series 2: Correspondence
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Letter from Paula Strain to Mary Feldman with visit suggestions, 10-Aug (Item 1)
    - Letter from Gilda Nimer to Mary Feldman with visit suggestions, 10-May-90 (Item 2)
    - Handwritten notecard with suggestions, undated (Item 3)
    - Letter from Mary Feldman to all members, May 15, 1993, 15-May-93 (Item 4)
    - Letter to Mary Feldman about meeting at Rock Creek Church Cemetery (undated) (Item 5)
    - Letter from Mary Feldman to Didi, undated (Item 6)
    - Letter from Vera Dickey to ALL seeking volunteer tutors dated August 14, 1987 (Item 7)
    - Letter from Tracy Casorso to Evelyn Fass seeking researchers interested in free-lancing dtd April 22, 1987, 22-Apr-87 (Item 8)
    - Announcement of research service, INQUIRE, at GW Gelman Library, 9-Oct-87 (Item 9)
    - Letter from Paula Strain to Mary Feldman identifying card catalog case for pickup, 10-Feb-97 (Item 10)
    - Draft fax from Mary Feldman to Catherine Scott dated 6/7/97, 7-Jun-97 (Item 11)
    - General Letter to All and Sundry from Mary Feldman, 16-Sep-88 (Item 12)
- Series 3: Ephemera
  - Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Obituary of Irwin Fass, undated (Item 1)
    - Info-Pak from National Gerontology Resource Center, Apr-89 (Item 2)
    - AARP info package, Jul-91 (Item 3)
    - Dupont Kalorama Museum Walk brochure, undated (Item 4)
    - American Libraries, May 1983, p. 278-284. Life after liberation: retirement planning for librarians, May-83 (Item 5)
    - Handwritten notes on envelope, undated. (Item 6)
    - Tally of ballots and restaurant menu, 1986 (Item 7)
    - National Trust's Master Places brochure, May, 1997 (Item 8)
    - Washington Theological Union's Connelly Chapel, May, 1997 (Item 9)
    - business cards of Museum employees, undated (Item 10)
    - Fatal Attraction: The Death and Life of Artist Carroll Sockwell, Washington Post, 9/27/92, 27-Sep (Item 11)
    - Gardeners' Specialities, Washington Post, 1/4/1996 (Item 12)
    - Treasure Houses of Washington, Washington Post, 1/17/1992 (Item 13)
    - Rose Hill Manor, Frederick, MD article in Washington Post, undated (Item 14)
    - Ladew Topiary Gardens, Harford County, MD, article in Washington Post, 8/19/1994 (Item 15)
- Series 4: Meeting Minutes
  - Meeting Minutes (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Report of the Association of Liberated Librarians for 1992-1993 (Item 1)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians Report: Sept 1986 to May 1987, Sep-86 (Item 2)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians Report: Sept 1985 to May 1986, Sep-85 (Item 3)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians Report: January - August 1984, Jan-84 (Item 4)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians Summary of activities, May - October 1983, May-83 (Item 5)
    - ALL Report from Evelyn FASS to Librarians' committee May 6, 1983, 6-May-83 (Item 6)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians final report following April 26 visit to Hagerstown and annual ballot, April 6 (Item 7)
- Series 5: Membership
  - Membership (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ALA Chapter Councilor announcement, Apr-96 (Item 1)
    - draft membership list, 1994-1995 (Item 2)
    - ALL (Association of Liberated Librarians) 3.5 diskette labeled 10/31 - 11/3 1997, undated (Item 3)
- Series 6: Newsletters
  - Newsletters (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Happy Holiday Newsletter, undated (Item 1)
    - ALL (The Association of Liberated Librarians), undated (Item 2)
    - Announcement of tour of the Library of the Comptroller of the Treasury on March 19, 1992, 1991-1992 (Item 3)
    - Announcement of the April 22nd meeting at the Association of Retired Persons, 1991-1992 (Item 4)
    - Announcement of Spring Picnic, May 29 at Rock Creek Cemetery, 1991-1992 (Item 5)
    - Announcement of the final meeting of the season, June 19, 1991, at the Music Library at University of Maryland College Park, 1991-1992 (Item 6)
    - September 1985 draft News release: The Association of Liberated Librarians, Sep-85 (Item 7)
    - Holiday newsletter and volunteer opportunities announcement, undated (Item 8)
    - Announcement of October 26, 1988 visit to the New Dept of Education Library, 26-Oct-88 (Item 9)
    - Announcement of February 8, 1990 visit to the Canadian Embassy Library and volunteer opportunities, 8-Feb-90 (Item 10)
    - Supplemental Issue: job and volunteer opportunities, 1988-1991 (Item 11)
    - Announcement of October 24, 1990 visit to Collington Retirement Community, 1988-1991 (Item 12)
    - Announcement of March 9, 1991 visit to the National Restaurant Association, 1988-1991 (Item 13)
    - Announcement of April 23, 1991 visit to Washington National Cathedral and Library, 1988-1991 (Item 14)
    - Announcement of May 19, 1987 brown bag lunch at Metropolitan Library Council, 19-May-87 (Item 15)
    - Announcement of Sept 16, 1987 brown bag lunch at Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, 16-Sep-87 (Item 16)
    - Announcement of February 8, 1990 visit to the Canadian Embassy Library and volunteer opportunities, 8-Feb-90 (Item 17)
    - Supplemental Issue: job and volunteer opportunities, 1988-1991 (Item 18)
- Series 7: Programs
  - Programs (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Lead to Read volunteer training program teaching adults to read, undated (Item 1)
    - Older Americans Consumer Cooperative, a not-for-profit consumer health care organization, seeking volunteers to help automate information and retrieval services (librarians), 25-Mar-85 (Item 2)
    - Library, Archives and Museum of the House of the Temple visit, April 8, 1998, 4/8/1998 (Item 3)
    - National Defense University visit on 12/2/1993, Dec-93 (Item 4)
    - Mongolian exhibit at National Geographic draft announcement, undated (Item 5)
    - Announcement of October 27, 1987 tour of National Geographic Society Library (Item 6)
    - Sackler GAllery brochure, 12/8/1988 (Item 7)
    - Announcement of December 8, 1988 visit to Sackler Gallery of Art and volunteer opportunities (Item 8)
    - National Museum of American Jewish Military History 5/26/1995 Final Meeting of 1994-1995 (Item 9)
    - Announcement of tour of National Presbyterian Church Library on November 7, 1991, 11/7/1991 (Item 10)
    - National Press Club visit, 01/23/1992, Jan-92 (Item 11)
    - DCLA announcementWoodrow Wilson House brochure (2), Feb-97 (Item 12)
    - Woodrow Wilson House - A National Trust Historic Site (2), Feb-97 (Item 13)
- Series 8: Site Visits
  - Alexandria Old Town (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Parking in Old Town Alexandria, 1994-1995 (Item 1)
    - The Seaport Inn Menu fro lunch and dinner, 1994-1995 (Item 2)
    - Visit the Alexandria Archeology Museum brochure, undated (Item 3)
    - Membership list, undated (Item 4)
    - The Alexandria Archeology Museum visit on 2/26/1995 (Item 5)
    - Parking in Old Town Alexandria, undated (Item 6)
    - rescheduled visit to Alexandria Archeology Museum on April 16, 1995, 4/16/1995 (Item 7)
  - AIA Library (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - AIA Library and Archives Fact Sheet, May-98 (Item 1)
    - AIA Library and Archives brochure, May-98 (Item 2)
    - American Institute of Architecture visit, May 1, 1998, 1-May-98 (Item 3)
  - Anderson House (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anderson House brochure, undated (Item 1)
    - SLA Chapter Notes - April 1997, Apr-97 (Item 2)
    - The Society of the Cinncinnati visit /14/1997, 14-May-97 (Item 3)
  - DC Historical Society (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Historical Society of Washington, DC brochure, Mar-97 (Item 1)
    - The Historical Society of Washington, DC Research Library brochure, undated (Item 2)
    - Two things to Mention in February and March (1997), Feb-97 (Item 3)
    - Announcement of February 28 visit to The Historical Society of Washington, DC (old Christian Heurich Mansion) and volunteer ops, Feb-97 (Item 4)
  - Dumbarton Oaks (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - DRAFT Dumbarton Oaks visit June 21, 1997, 21-Jun-97 (Item 1)
    - Dumbarton Oaks visit, 12/3/1992 (Item 2)
    - Dumbarton Oaks visit, 12/3/1992 (Item 3)
    - participation questionnaire, undated (Item 4)
  - Fannie Mae (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - draft newsletter Corporate Library of Fannie Mae visit on 12/7/1995 (Item 1)
    - volunteer position available, Youth for Understanding, Information center collecting info on telcoms in Latin American countries (back page of newsletter), 1-May-98 (Item 2)
    - Meeting rescheduled - Corporate Library of Fannie Mae, on 2/9/1996, 1-May-98 (Item 3)
    - Housing Research News - Fannie Mae, 1995 (Item 4)
    - Fannie Mae - The Corporate Library Brochure (2), 1995 (Item 5)
    - handwritten note from Fannie Mae Library director, undated (Item 6)
  - Foundation Center (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Announcement of Invitation for January 13, 1991 visit to the Foundation Center, 1/13/1991 (Item 1)
    - Brochure from The Foundation Center Washington Office, undated (Item 2)
    - Letter from Margot Brinkley, Foundation Center Director, to Mary Feldman, extending invitation to visit The Foundation Center, 8-Jan-91 (Item 3)
  - Gadsby's Tavern (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Gadsby's Tavern visit, December 12, 1997, undated (Item 1)
    - Gadsby's Tavern Museum, Dec-97 (Item 2)
  - George Washington Masonic (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - George Washington Masonic National Memorial brochure, undated (Item 1)
    - George Washington Masonic National Memorial visit on 3/9/1994 (Item 2)
    - George Washington Masonic National Memorial brochure, undated (Item 3)
  - Heurich House Museum (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Washington Post clipping May 4, 1990 Heurich Mansion, 4-May-90 (Item 1)
    - Historical Society of Washington, DC, Black and White and Red, White and Blue, undated (Item 2)
    - Metro History News - Winter 96/97 newsletter, Winter 1996 (Item 3)
    - Metro History News - Spring 97 newsletter, Spring 1997 (Item 4)
    - The Heurich House Museum brochure, undated (Item 5)
  - Hillwood Museum (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Hillwood Museum visit, 09/19/1997 (Item 1)
    - Newspaper clipping from April 24, 1981 Washington Post on Hillwood House, 24-Apr-81 (Item 2)
    - Brochure and map on Hillwood, undated (Item 3)
    - Hillwood Museum brochure, undated (Item 4)
    - Hillwood Museum and Garden ticket stub, 9/19/1997 (Item 5)
    - Letter from Mary Feldman to Hillwood Museum Confirming reservation for visit on Sept 5, 1997, 6/23/1997 (Item 6)
  - Howard University (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Howard University Founders Library and the Moorland-Spingarn Research Center, 10/22/1992, undated (Item 1)
    - Howard University Libraries Student Guide to Research and Documentation, Oct-92 (Item 2)
    - Howard University Founders Library and the Moorland-Spingarn Research Center, 10/22/1992, Oct-92 (Item 3)
    - various brochures on Howard University libraries, research center, architecture, quick guide, giude to literrary criticism, Oct-92 (Item 4)
  - John Hager House, Hagerstown (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Announcement of April 26, 1990 all day outing in Hagerstown, MD, 26-Apr-90 (Item 1)
    - Letter from Paula Strain to Mary Feldman dtd April 6, 1990 RE: April 26 Program in Hagerstown, 6-Apr-90 (Item 2)
    - Association of Liberated Librarians draft report following April 26 outing in Hagerstown, MD, 26-Apr-90 (Item 3)
  - Kennedy Center (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Announcement of March 8, 1988 visit to the Performing Arts Library at the Kennedy Center and volunteer opportunities, 8-Mar-88 (Item 1)
    - Announcement of volunteer opportunities at the Issac Frank Jewish Public Library and several job opportunities, 8-Mar-88 (Item 2)
    - Announcement of October 26, 1987 visit to the Performing Arts Library at the Kennedy Center and job opportunitiews, 26-Oct-87 (Item 3)
  - Korea Information Center (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Korean Information Center visit on 11/9/1995 (Item 1)
    - draft letter to director of Korean Information center, undated (Item 2)
    - Volunteer position available, Youth for Understanding, Information center collecting info on telcoms in Latin American countries (back page of newsletter), 11/9/1995 (Item 3)
    - Korean Overseas Information Service publication - The Koreans, undated (Item 4)
    - chopsticks - Jin-ga, undated (Item 5)
    - The Korean Information Center brochure (with sections cut out), undated (Item 6)
    - handwritten note from member regarding Korean Information Center, 8/22/1995 (Item 7)
    - handwritten notes, 11/9/1995 (Item 8)
    - Seoul: The Monthly Magazine of Korea Illustrated - Oct 1995, Oct-95 (Item 9)
  - Kreeger House (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - draft letter to Kreeger Museum and Art Gallery 4/9/97, Apr-97 (Item 1)
    - The Kreeger Museum Scherzo-Duetto b W.A. Mozart brochure (2), Apr-97 (Item 2)
    - Washington Post article, May 29, 1994, p. G6, Kreeger Museum, May-94 (Item 3)
    - handwritten note from Shirley Tuthill to Mary Feldman about visit to Kreeger House, Apr-97 (Item 4)
    - The Kreeger Museum and Art Gallery visit 4/23/1997, Apr-97 (Item 5)
  - Library of Congress (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Library of Congress The Digital Visitor's Center visit 05/31/1996, 31-May-96 (Item 1)
    - Creating a National Library info sheet, undated (Item 2)
    - Internet Resources for the public: LC web, undated (Item 3)
    - Internet Resources for the public: LOCIS, undated (Item 4)
    - Facts about the Library of Congress (for FY 1994), undated (Item 5)
    - List of all American Memory Collections and Topics, undated (Item 6)
    - Library of Congress (LC) Electronic Resources, undated (Item 7)
    - Internet resources for the public: World Wide Web, undated (Item 8)
    - Internet Resources for the public: The Library of Congress Gopher: LC Marvel, undated (Item 9)
    - Copyright Office, Library of Congress CORDS, undated (Item 10)
    - Library of Congress Technology Environment Overview, undated (Item 11)
    - Library of Congress National Ddigital Library Multimedia Historical Collections, undated (Item 12)
    - Internet access to LOCIS Library of Congress Information System, undated (Item 13)
    - THOMAS - Legislative Information on the internet, undated (Item 14)
  - Montgomery County Library (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Brochure of telephone reference service at Montgomery County Public Library, undated (Item 1)
    - Announcement of March 11, 1988 library tour of the Montgomery County Historical Society Library and 19th century Beall-Dawson House in Rockville, MD, 11-Mar-88 (Item 2)
    - Announcement of September 28, 1989 visit to the Telephone Reference Service at Montgomery County Dept of Public Libraries, 28-Sep-89 (Item 3)
    - Montgomery County Historical Society, 03/11/1997 (Item 4)
    - Beale-Dawson House, Rockville, MD 03/11/1997 (Item 5)
  - NARA (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - National Archives 1994 brochure (Item 1)
    - NARA Library News newsletter, undated (Item 2)
    - Select Audiovisual Records - Pictures of the American City (2), undated (Item 3)
    - Information for Researchers - National Archives at College Park (2), undated (Item 4)
    - The National Archives - Information for Visitors, undated (Item 5)
    - National Archives Library visit on 10/27/1994, undated (Item 6)
    - the National Archives Library staff and floor plan, undated (Item 7)
    - handwritten notes (back of envelope), undated (Item 8)
  - National Building Museum (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Letters between Mary Feldman and Michael Kruelle arranging Oct 20, 1997 visit of the National Building Museum, June 11. 1997 (Item 1)
    - Announcement of Oct 20, 1997 visit of the National Building Museum, 20-Oct-97 (Item 2)
    - National Building Museum brochures, tour information, and event calendar, June, 1997 (Item 3)
  - NFATC (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - visit request letter to NFATC (National Foreign Affairs Traning Center), dtd 12/14/1993, Dec-93 (Item 1)
    - National Foreign Affairs Training Center visit, 02/17/1994, Feb-94 (Item 2)
    - Volunteer position available, St. Luke Institute (back page of newsletter), Feb-94 (Item 3)
    - Welcome to the National Foreign Affairs Training Center and map, undated (Item 4)
    - draft letter to National Foreign Affairs Training Center, 14-Dec-93 (Item 5)
  - National Gallery of Art (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The National Gallery of Art Library visit 4/24/1996 (Item 1)
    - Volunteer position available - MRRC Library. 3/15/1996 (Item 2)
    - Draft thank you letter to National Art Gallery Librarian, 5/15/1996 (Item 3)
    - National Gallery of Art Photographic Archives brochure, undated (Item 4)
    - Staff Guide - The National Gallery of Art Slide Library, undated (Item 5)
    - The Public Lending Guide - The National Gallery of Art Slide Library, undated (Item 6)
    - Photocopy of architectural drawing (G Sangallo GDSU 2043 A verso), undated (Item 7)
    - National Gallery of Art Library brochure, undated (Item 8)
  - National Museum of African Art (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Calendar of special programs - National Museum of African art, undated (Item 1)
    - National Museum of African Art brochure, undated (Item 2)
    - Educational programs 1996-1997 - National Museum of African Art, Jan-97 (Item 3)
    - Eliot Elisofon Photographic Archives brochure, Jan-97 (Item 4)
    - Calendar Fall 1996 - National Museum of African Art, Jan-97 (Item 5)
    - Ancient Nubia brochure - National Museum of African Art, Jan-97 (Item 6)
    - Letter to Warren M. Robbins Library Director, Jan-97 (Item 7)
    - Bookmark, Smithsonian Insttitution Libraries, Jan-97 (Item 8)
    - Smithsonian Libraries - Libraries Acquisition List, No. 177, Jan-97 (Item 9)
    - Nigerian Artists - A Who's Who, brochure, Jan-97 (Item 10)
    - Ceramic Gestures - New Vessels by Magdalene Odundo - brochure, Jan-97 (Item 11)
    - photocopy of article on Museum of African Art, from December 15, 1996, p. G10, Jan-97 (Item 12)
    - photocopy of exhibition announcement, Memory: Luba art, Jan-97 (Item 13)
    - photocopy of exhibition announcement, Memory: Luba art DTD Jan 6, Jan-97 (Item 14)
    - African Art Index - January 6, 1997 (2), Jan-97 (Item 15)
    - The National Museum of African Art Library brochure (2), Jan-97 (Item 16)
    - Smithsonian Institution Libraries User guide brochure, Jan-97 (Item 17)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Announcement of November 14,1997 visit to National Museum of Women in the Arts, 14-Nov-97 (Item 1)
    - Spring 1997 issue of The National Museum of Women in the Arts (Item 2)
    - Announcement of December 8, 1987 library tour of National Museum of Women in the Arts, 12/8/1987 (Item 3)
    - Women in the Arts, Washington Post, 12/24/1992, undated (Item 4)
  - Oatlands (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - draft letter to membership proposing Oatlands visit between SLA and ALA,May 19, 1997, 19-May-97 (Item 1)
    - The Gardens at Oatlands brochure, undated (Item 2)
    - Volunteer announcement, Oatlands, Cataloging, 1997 (Item 3)
    - The Oatlands Column, Winter 1996, newsletter (Item 4)
    - From the Garden. Oatlands, undated (Item 5)
    - Oatlands, Montgomery Journal, July 29, 1983, 29-Jul-83 (Item 6)
  - Postal Museum (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - The Postal Museum visit 3/20/1996 (Item 1)
    - Letter from Postal Museum Branch Librarian, 10/7/1993 (Item 2)
    - Smithsonian Museum Archival, Manuscript, and Special Collection Resources brochure, undated (Item 3)
    - The National Postal Museum brochure, undated (Item 4)
    - National Postal Museum Information for Group Visits, undated (Item 5)
    - United States Postal Museum visit on 10/20/1993 (Item 6)
  - Rock Creek Park (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Rock Creek Cemetery Bulletin, Vol. 2, No. 2, Winter, 1991 (Item 1)
    - Rock Creek Cemetery Brochure on The Adams Memorial, May 20, 1990, 20-May-90 (Item 2)
  - Textile Museum (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - The Textile Museum visit on 11/22/1994 (Item 1)
    - The Textile Museum brochure, undated (Item 2)
    - Rugs and Textiles of Late Imperial China, undated (Item 3)
    - handwritten note from Margaret Missar to Mary Feldman proposing the Textile Museum for a visit, 7/29/1994 (Item 4)
    - Textile Museum article from Washington Post, June 18, 1994, 18-Jun-94 (Item 5)
    - Textile Museum brochure, Islamic Embroidery stitch, May 27, 1994, 27-May-84 (Item 6)
    - Textile Museum brochure, Textiles about Textiles, April 8, 1994, 8-Apr-94 (Item 7)
    - Textile Museum Arthur D. Jenkins Library, undated (Item 8)
    - Textile Museum Han Woman's Quasi-Official Vest, undated (Item 9)
    - Textile Museum brochure, Native American Art from Oklahoma,Nov 18, 1994, undated (Item 10)
    - Textile Museum brochure, undated (Item 11)
  - Transafrica (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Transafrica Forum brochure, undated (Item 1)
    - torn page from the Smithsonian Magazine January 1995 - Study Tours, Jan-95 (Item 2)
    - Transafrica Forum Calendar of Events (including newsclips) (2), undated (Item 3)
    - Transafrica Forum visit on November 15,1996, Nov-96 (Item 4)
    - Sept-Oct 1996 Bimonthly Bulletin of TransAfrica Forum Activities, Sep-96 (Item 5)
  - Tudor Place (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Tudor Place visit, 09/24/1992, undated (Item 1)
    - Washington Post Style section, p. F1, October 16, 1988, article on Tudor Place, Oct-88 (Item 2)
    - Welcome back for 1992-1993 Meetings, Tudor Place visit, 09/24/1992, Sep-92 (Item 3)
    - Washington Post, p. F6, June 5, 1988, article on Tudor Place, Jun-88 (Item 4)
    - Tudor Place Foundation visit confirmation, 09/24/1992, Sep-92 (Item 5)
  - USA Today (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - USA Today LIbrary and Research Service visit 12/9/1996 (Item 1)